<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sections on Afrotech Fest</title>
    <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sections on Afrotech Fest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Afrotech Fest. Made with &amp;#10084; in London</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:19 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/about/</guid>
      <description>.pattern-14 { width: 60%; max-width: 12rem; top: 250px; right: -50px; z-index: -1; }    .pattern-16 { width: 60%; max-width: 40rem; top: 450px; right: -500px; animation: pulse 5s infinite ease-in-out normal; }     ABOUT THE FESTIVAL Afrotech Fest is a two-day tech and digital festival by and for black people of African and Caribbean heritage. The&amp;nbsp;festival won’t replicate models for tech events, festivals and conferences that currently exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/who/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/who/</guid>
      <description>WHO IS IT FOR? AfroTech Fest is a place for black African and Caribbean people interested in technology. We take our motto “Join us and find your people,” to heart. Therefore we are actively engaged in connecting people like us, so that we can build a technological future that is for us. AfroTech fest is for black geeks, techies, weirdos and nerds, for anyone who has noticed that they are the only black face in the room, for anyone who has ever wondered “Why is my technology white?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submit</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/submit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/submit/</guid>
      <description>SUBMIT A PROPOSAL We&amp;rsquo;re casting the net far and wide to find some of the most interesting, diverse and forward-thinking people in our community. We are very keen to hear from techies, artists, enthusiasts and community workers whose aims resonate with ours. If you have an idea for a workshop or a talk, a suggestion about who or what else should be included, or even a topic that you feel should be addressed, then fill out our proposal form or get in touch below!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/venue/</guid>
      <description> THE VENUE Richmix is an independent arts venue in the heart of the East London. It was established in 2004 and has gone on to become one of the largest and most relevant arts venues in the capital. Rich Mix is spread over five floors, is fully accessible, contains three cinemas, flexible performance spaces and plenty of room for a big ideas festival like ours.
[INSERT IMAGES OF VENUE] </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:53:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>SPONSORSHIP We would love you to get involved if you are interested in inspiring young people to develop an interest in making things and problem-solving, or in helping create a space to address issues of access in tech industries for black peoples of all ages and abilities in the UK. Supporting our work is a great way to show your commitment to marginalised communities, and for you to access a wealth of talent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/team/</guid>
      <description>.pattern-29 { max-width: 30rem; top: -17px; right: -200px; z-index: -1; }    .pattern-31 { max-width: 30rem; top: 130px; right: -500px; z-index: -1; }    .pattern-35 { max-width: 40rem; top: 250px; right: -300px; }     THE TEAM We’re a team of activists, artists, techies and community leaders who are focused on black communities in the UK. Afrotech Fest seeks to bring together these strands, specifically serving black people and creating conversations and connections beyond ‘networking’ or bending to fit into the current industries and climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:58:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/contact/</guid>
      <description>GET IN TOUCH We would love to hear from interested sponsors, possible speakers, or workshop facilitators or anyone interested in knowing more about the event.
General enquiries can be sent to info@afrotechfest.co.uk or debs@afrotechfest.co.uk
CODE OF CONDUCT
ACCESSIBILITY AND INCLUSION
FAQs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Footer</title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/footer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:08:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/footer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://afrotechfest.co.uk/sections/home/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>